[Music]
for most of my life I didn't live in a
place that has such distinct changes of
Seasons as where I live now in the
winter while I often miss the warmth and
the feeling of the earth beneath my bare
feet I have to admit December is so
beautiful when all is bathed in and
white it feels like a story book and I
can find myself losing sense of time as
I watch the snowflakes fall outside of
my
window winter is certainly a season
meant for
[Music]
dreaming
many years ago during a challenging
chapter of my story I found that I'd
become someone that was terrified of
stepping out of their comfort zone and
into the unknown in an attempt to become
healthier I read a book about the
importance of expanding your world
whenever you're trying to overcome a
personal issue whether it's a mental or
more physical challenge anything from
overcoming poor self steam anxiety body
image or honestly
[Music]
anything
it is so easy to become consumed by our
own problems and while everyone's
journey to Healing is different one
crucial part for me was expanding my
world in my case this meant getting a
job someplace that helped me socialize
in a safe space until I regained my
confidence like working at my local
bookstore I tried new hobbies and did my
best not to give up just because I
wasn't perfect at them I met new people
and habitually pushed myself out of my
safe Zone in small ways slowly becoming
more comfortable with
[Music]
discomfort you see these may seem like
obvious simple steps to improving one's
life but what it taught me was something
very
[Music]
powerful
so it just started snowing outside which
is so exciting because that was not on
the forecast and I thought what better
way to spend the afternoon then reading
and enjoying some very special festive
desserts which I'm going to work on in
just a few minutes as many of you know I
had my birthday recently and I was
gifted by my lovely mother of the
emerald sea I think she was attracted to
the beautiful designs on the inside and
this photo that I think reminded her of
me in some way though I have no plans to
be going on a wild pirating Adventure
anytime soon and then since I work at a
bookstore I am aware of new releases and
one that caught my eye was Crest Water
Crest by Gregory Maguire I've not heard
this book mentioned anywhere and I think
it deserves a lot more recognition
because
the illustrations are absolutely
enchanting and they're throughout the
entire book and it's all about the story
of Little Rabbit named Crest who is
trying to find her new home and her
sense of belonging after some difficult
circumstances befall her little family I
decided that I would also have on hand a
copy of Tasha Tudor's fairy tales
because this is a very prized possession
of mine and every Christmas I try to
read at least one story from this book
The illustrations again are absolutely
delightful and they always fill me with
that kind of sense of being a child
again and just being cozied up at home
so it seems like it will be an
absolutely lovely way to spend a Snowy
Evening however I do have to try to make
the recipe I was thinking about it is
kind of self-created so we're going to
see if it works out I had some fruit and
other items that I wanted to use up
before the end of the week and so we're
going to do a little bit of
experimentation in the
kitchen
when you expand your world beyond the
confines of the struggles you are facing
you slowly begin to realize that what
you're struggling with doesn't need to
be your entire world it can be a part of
who you are in the present
but by no means does it Define you or
dictate your worth and it certainly
doesn't need to be in your future things
change we grow and the mountains we
never thought we'd be able to climb
start to look like hills in hindsight
and that's a hard thing to believe but I
needed to believe it to go forward and
in the beauty of that Journey you become
aware that you are
strong looking back it's hard to believe
I wasted so much of my life minutes
worrying about my body my achievements
other's opinions of me the list is never
ending thankfully at long last I got
tired of that burden and decided enough
is enough and stopped expecting
Perfection instead I tried to put my
energy into practicing humility and
gentleness towards myself learning to
live this way feels like tapping into a
lasting piece that sacred Essence that
feels wise and true in your
soul I wish you the best for the new
year and I wish you to be
[Music]
free
so I just picked this box up in the mail
not too long ago and it has some gifts
in it from a very lovely soul I just had
to show you the gifts because clearly
there was so much time put into wrapping
them what an
enchanting wrapping paper design and the
ribbon and everything it's just so
beautiful so inside I received some
socks a bunny sweater very beautiful
beautiful journal and some beeswax wraps
which I absolutely love I'm definitely
going to be using these I was also given
this very beautiful baby gift among
several other gifts but I didn't want to
be here forever so I just wanted to show
some that were really sweet it felt so
festive and like such a fun activity to
unwrap some beautiful gifts maybe it
will inspire you to give your friend or
loved one a beautifully wrapped gift
this December because there's something
so special about that added touch with
that being said I am so appreciative of
all the love kindness and support I have
gotten from so many people this time of
year especially with our lovely news of
our baby we just had another doctor's
appointment and we got to listen to an
extremely healthy heartbeat it was such
a moving and fascinating and wondrous
experience and we are so excited for the
future and I really deeply appreciate
all of you and thank you so so much I
hope this festive season is a magical
one for you and I'm sending you so much
love
goodbye